Guide to the Fashion Moda Archive MSS.091
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series III: Artists, Exhibitions, and Related Material
  - Subseries H: Video - Originals
    - [1.] -- Slow Scan Tele Conference [2.] -- Manhattan/Bronx; 3/6/1979 and 3/7/1979., cuid9463 (Box 19, Folder ID: 091.0029)
      3/4" Umatic videocassette. Tape length 20 minutes.
    - Fashion Moda Documentary, July 4, 1982., cuid9464 (Box 19, Folder ID: 091.0026)
      1/2" VHS videocassette PAL. Tape length 120 minutes.
    - Making Coincidences, February 5, 1984., cuid9465 (Box 16, Folder ID: 091.0001)
    - Making Coincidences, February 12, 1984., cuid9466 (Box 16, Folder ID: 091.0002)
    - Making Coincidences, February 19, 1984., cuid9467 (Box 16, Folder ID: 091.0003)
    - Making Coincidences, February 26, 1984., cuid9468 (Box 16, Folder ID: 091.0004)
    - Making Coincidences, March 4, 1984., cuid9469 (Box 16, Folder ID: 091.0005)
    - Making Coincidences, March 18, 1984., cuid9470 (Box 16, Folder ID: 091.0006)
    - Making Coincidences, March 25, 1984., cuid9471 (Box 16, Folder ID: 091.0007)
    - Making Coincidences, April 1, 1984., cuid9472 (Box 17, Folder ID: 091.0008)
    - Making Coincidences, April 8, 1984., cuid9473 (Box 17, Folder ID: 091.0009)
    - Making Coincidences, April 15, 1984 (as per cassette)/April 22, 1984 (as per container)., cuid9474 (Box 17, Folder ID: 091.0010)
    - Making Coincidences, April 29 & May 6, 1984., cuid9475 (Box 17, Folder ID: 091.0011)
    - Making Coincidences, May 13, 1984., cuid9476 (Box 17, Folder ID: 091.0012)
    - Making Coincidences, May 27, 1984., cuid9477 (Box 17, Folder ID: 091.0013)
    - Making Coincidences, May 27, 1984., cuid9478 (Box 17, Folder ID: 091.0014)
    - Making Coincidences, June 3, 1984., cuid9479 (Box 18, Folder ID: 091.0015)
    - Making Coincidences, X. Y. C., n. d.., 1984; cuid9480 (Box 18, Folder ID: 091.0016)
    - Stefan Eins Presents: July 11 and 21, 1986., cuid9481 (Box 18, Folder ID: 091.0017)
    - Stefan Eins Presents: 2/25/1987., cuid9482 (Box 18, Folder ID: 091.0018)
    - Stefan Eins Presents: edit in process, March 25, 1987., cuid9483 (Box 18, Folder ID: 091.0019)
    - Commercials for Stefan, n. d., 1987; cuid9484 (Box 18, Folder ID: 091.0020)
    - Colab extinction, n. d., undated; cuid9485 (Box 19, Folder ID: 091.0025)
      Betamax
    - Fashion Moda Gallery- South Bronx, tape 1., undated; cuid9486 (Box 19, Folder ID: 091.0027)
    - Graffiti., undated; cuid9487 (Box 19, Folder ID: 091.0028)
    - Barbara Smith Fashion Moda Request E., undated; cuid9488 (Box 19, Folder ID: 091.0030)
      1/2" VHS videocassette PAL. Tape length 30 minutes.
    - Unidentified video tape., undated; cuid9489 (Box 19, Folder ID: 091.0031)
- Oversize: Series II: Fashion Moda as a Business
  - Subseries A: Administrative Files
    - Ongoing renovations., undated; cuid9490 (Box 20, Folder 7)
- Oversize: Series III: Artists, Exhibitions, and Related Materials
  - Subseries A: Artist Files
    - Science, Invention, Technology, Art and Fantasy, images used for first exhibition, 1978 [see also I. 1. 7A], cuid9492 (Box 22, Folder 3 - 3.2)
    - "Science, Invention, Technology, Art and Fantasy", production material 1978 [see also I. 1. 7A], cuid9493 (Box 22, Folder 2 - 2.1)
    - Designs for Documenta 7 t-shirts, 1982. [No Duplication Allowed], cuid9494 (Box 24, Folder 17)
    - Holzer, Jenny: "Truisms", for Documenta 7, 1982.[No Duplication Allowed], cuid9495 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Production Materials for Documenta 7 Store, 1982.[No Duplication Allowed], cuid9496 (Box 24, Folder 16)
    - Production Materials for Documenta 7, transparencies. [No Duplication Allowed], undated; cuid9497 (Box 24, Folder 15)
    - Science, Art, Design, Invention, Technology, Fantasy, a brochure, 1984, cuid9498 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Oversize: Series III, Subseries B: Exhibition Promotion.
    - Flyers and Posters, 1979- 1981; cuid9499 (Box 24, Folder 12 - 12.1)
    - Flyers and Posters, 1983- 1988; cuid9500 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Flyers and Posters, 1989- 1993; cuid9501 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Flyers and Posters, n. d., undated; cuid9502 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Articles on Fashion Moda, 1981; cuid9503 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Articles on Fashion Moda, n. d., undated; cuid9504 (Box 24, Folder 13)
    - Announcements from other galleries., undated; cuid9505 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Oversize: Series III, Subseries C: Photographs.
    - Eins, Stefan, Jones, Baird & Mark Kostabi, 1985- 1986; cuid9506 (Box 21, Folder 25)
  - Oversize: Series III, Subseries D: Artworks.
    - Aone, painting. (tag) [No Duplication Allowed], undated; cuid9507 (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - Crash, painting. (tag) [No Duplication Allowed], undated; cuid9508 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Eins, Stefan: painting (tag, drawing), undated; cuid9509 (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - Fekner, John: drawing for Documenta 7. [No Duplication Allowed], undated; cuid9510 (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - Haring, Keith: drawing for Documenta 7.[No Duplication Allowed], undated; cuid9511 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Mullican Matt: poster, undated; cuid9512 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Nenner, Paulette: drawing. [No Duplication Allowed], undated; cuid9513 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Pou, Alyson: collage. [No Duplication Allowed], undated; cuid9514 (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - Scharf, Kenny: drawings for Documenta 7.[No Duplication Allowed], undated; cuid9515 (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Toxic, drawing. (tag), undated; cuid9516 (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - G-Man, Tag, undated; cuid9517 (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - van Dalen, Anton: drawing for Documenta 7 [No Duplication Allowed], undated; cuid9518 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Wells, David: drawing for Documenta 7. [No Duplication Allowed], undated; cuid9519 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Y-Pants, drawing, undated; cuid9520 (Box 21, Folder 25)
    - unidentified drawing, undated; cuid9521 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Oversize: Series III, Subseries H: Video - Originals
    Subseries H: Video - Originals
    Audiovisual materials have not been preserved and may not be available.
    - Making Coincidences, title cards., undated; cuid9522 (Box 24, Folder 1)
- Over-Oversize: Series I: Fashion Moda Overview
  - Cooney, Robert "Por Exxon, for Kill", painting., undated; cuid9523 (Flat-file-folder 30)
  - Eins, Stefan "Billiard/Pool for Random Objects", instructions., undated; cuid9524 (Box 22, Folder 1)
- Over-Oversize: Series III: Artists, Exhibitions, and Related Materials
  - Subseries A: Administrative Files
    - Eins, Stefan: poster., undated; cuid9525 (Flat-file-folder 32)
    - Evans, Andrea: proposal., undated; cuid9526 (Box 20)
  - Subseries B: Grants and Fundraising
    - flyers and poster, 1983-1987; cuid9527 (Flat-file-folder 33)
  - Subseries D: Artworks
    - Kostner, Arthur: two drawings., undated; cuid9528 (Flat-file-folder 31)
    - Fashion Moda Portfolio., undated; cuid9529 (Folder 8)